William H. Ellis Letters
William H. Ellis Letters
1835-1838
Ellis, William H., fl. 1835-1838.
17 items (SC)
Ellis was superintendent of lighthouses in Connecticut and New Hampshire. Letters from S. Pleasonton, 5th Auditor and Acting Commissioner of Revenue, Treasury Department, concerning building and repairing lighthouses, behavior of attendants, and appointments.
149205
Biographical History
William H. Ellis was the superintendent of lighthouses in Connecticut and New Hampshire during the first half of the 19th century.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The William H. Ellis Letters contain incoming correspondence from S. Pleasonton, 5th Auditor and Acting Commissioner of Revenue, Treasury Department. The correspondence concerns information on building and repairing lighthouses, the behavior of attendants, and appointments.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection contains one series, Correspondence, which is arranged chronologically.
Subject and Genre Headings
None; Ellis, William H., fl. 1835-1838.; Pleasonton, S.; Lighthouse keepers.; Lighthouses.; Correspondence.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Correspondence
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - 07 Apr 1835 (Sc 243)
    - 11 Apr 1835 (Sc 243)
    - 07 May 1835 (Sc 243)
    - 30 Jul 1835 (Sc 243)
    - 31 Aug 1835 (Sc 243)
    - 23 Oct 1835 (Sc 243)
    - 19 Dec 1835 (Sc 243)
    - 13 Mar 1837 (Sc 243)
    - 24 Jun 1837 (Sc 243)
    - 11 Jul 1838 (Sc 243)
    - 01 Aug 1838 (Sc 243)
    - 02 Aug 1838 (Sc 243)
    - 09 Aug 1838 (Sc 243)
    - 15 Aug 1838 (Sc 243)
    - 05 Sep 1838 (Sc 243)
    - 23 Nov 1838 (Sc 243)